5|God's Not Dead 2|When a high school teacher is asked a question in class about Jesus her reasoned response lands her in deep trouble and could expel God from the public square once and for all|229|2016|1|764ebc6e-af65-4476-8f68-70e34e5996aa|Harold Cronk|
10|Everybody Wants Some!!|A group of college baseball players navigate their way through the freedoms and responsibilities of unsupervised adulthood.|66|2016|6|7a494d4a-5d25-403a-82af-924e35255fd3|Richard Linklater|
11|Miles Ahead|An exploration of the life and music of Miles Davis.|229|2015|12|ef2f3269-b601-458d-9882-22986ffefe55|Don Cheadle|
12|The Dark Horse|An emotionally charged and inspiring drama about a man who searches for the courage to lead, despite his own adversities - finding purpose and hope in passing on his gift to the children in his community.|1|2014|21|1f3e9804-c4fc-4573-a05f-3173a8c4f2a2|James Napier Robertson|
13|Meet the Blacks|The Black family is getting out of Chicago in hopes of a better life. After Carl Black (Mike Epps) comes into some unexpected funds, he takes his family and leaves the hustling lifestyle behind for something better. Carl, his new wife Lorena (Zulay Henao), son Carl Jr., daughter Allie Black (Bresha Webb) and cousin Cronut (Lil Duval) pack up and move to Beverly Hills. Turns out, Carl couldn't have picked a worse time to move. They arrive right around the time of the annual purge, when all crime is legal for twelve hours.|1|2016|9|d7439867-1ece-4f9b-978b-b7bd042f8200|Deon Taylor|
14|Kill Your Friends|An A&R man working at the height of the Britpop music craze goes to extremes in order to find his next hit.|1|2015|11|a1e0c451-55ce-45e0-8aa5-85c774cc79e5|Owen Harris|
15|Natural Born Pranksters|YouTube's best pranksters, Roman Atwood, Vitaly Z, and Dennis Roady make the leap to the big screen.|14|2016|14|534b6fb1-5c72-4c2c-9bba-41d3b02f3133|Roman Atwood|
16|La tete haute|The story centers on a young delinquent as he comes of age.|229|2015|7|c3e7e364-21e6-428c-98cf-00bec2061106|Emmanuelle Bercot|
17|Zoothopie|In a city of anthropomorphic animals, a rookie bunny cop and a cynical con artist fox must work together to uncover a conspiracy.|159|2016|7|fc9433e4-d5f1-4844-94dc-41ca67db68f5|Byron Howard|
18|Divergente 3|After the earth-shattering revelations of Insurgent, Tris must escape with Four beyond the wall that encircles Chicago, to finally discover the shocking truth of the world around them.|229|2016|15|c77dc350-dcd7-45d4-931d-6fb404b657a8|Roert Schwentke|
19|Miracles from Heaven|A young girl suffering from a rare digestive disorder finds herself miraculously cured after surviving a terrible accident.|229|2016|9|6c38d67d-013c-45c1-aeb1-f4912886299a|Patricia Riggen|
21|10 Cloverfield Lane|After getting in a car accident, a woman is held in a shelter with two men, who claim the outside world is affected by a widespread chemical attack.|39|2016|11|02c87576-46e3-446c-ae49-63c1caa66724|Dan Trachtenberg|
